meetwalter.com 2017-04-16

# FoxPrivacy.com

To print this document, click here. 

Table of Contents: 

  1. INTRODUCTION
  2. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION 
  3. USE AND DISCLOSURE
  4. SECURITY
  5. USER ACCESS AND CONTROL 
  6. OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION 
  7. CONTACT US 

## 1\. INTRODUCTION

Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation (“Fox”) wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information from and about you. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information collected through services such as websites, mobile sites, and mobile applications (“apps”) (the “Fox Services”). By using Fox Services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. A list of our affiliated companies (“Company Affiliates”) is available at [www.21cf.com](http://www.21cf.com/). 

This Privacy Policy applies to Fox’s collection and use of your personal information and describes generally Fox’s practices for handling non-personal information. 

Other than as described below under the heading “Activity Information,” which is used to support the internal operations of Fox Services, we do not collect information from children under 13. Accordingly, on some of the Fox Services, children under 13 are not eligible to use certain features of the Fox Services. 

## 2\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

Fox and our service providers may collect the following information from and about you: 

**Registration Information** is the information eligible users submit to register for a Fox Service, for example, to create an account, post comments, receive a newsletter, or enter a contest.  Registration Information may include, for example, name, email address, gender, zip code and birthday. 

**Public Information and Posts** consist of comments or content that eligible users post to the Fox Services and the information about the user that accompanies those posts or content, which may include a name, user name, comments, likes, status, profile information and picture.  Public Information and Posts are always public, which means they are available to everyone and may be displayed in search results on external search engines. 

**Information from Social Media.** If you have a social media account and are eligible to access or log-in to a Fox Service through a social media service or connect a Fox Service to a social media service, the information we collect may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with that social media service, any information or content you have permitted the social media service to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends lists, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service.  When you access the Fox Services through social media services or when you connect a Fox Service to social media services, you are authorizing Fox to collect, store, and use such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Activity Information.** When you access and interact with the Fox Services, we may collect certain information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Fox Services, our servers receive and record information about your computer or device, and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the Fox Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other transactional information for that device. Fox uses these types of information to support the internal operations of the Fox Services. 

Our websites may use cookies and other similar technologies. Cookies and other similar technologies (such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies) are comprised of small bits of data. Fox's websites, apps and other services send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer or other device so the website or app can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that service. These technologies may also be used to collect and store information about your usage of the Fox Services, such as pages you have visited or the video and other content you have viewed. Fox uses these types of information to support the internal operations of the Fox Services. 

For certain features available to eligible users, third parties that support the Fox Services by providing services, such as compiling aggregate Fox Services usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information when you use the Company Services or third party services. Fox does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe’s website, see <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html>. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features, content or personalization. 

**Do Not Track.** At this time we do not respond to browser ‘Do Not Track’ signals, as we await the work of interested stakeholders and others to develop standards for how such signals should be interpreted. 

## 3\. USE AND DISCLOSURE

We use the information we collect from you to provide the Fox Services and features to you, including: to measure and improve those Fox Services and features; to improve your experience with both online and off-line Fox Services by allowing eligible users to comment on content, and participate in online games, sweepstakes or contests; to provide you with customer support and to respond to inquiries.  When the information collected from or about you does not identify you as a specific person, we may use that information for any purpose or share it with third parties to the extent permitted by applicable law. 

We may use the information we collect from and about you for these additional purposes: 

**To allow service providers to assist us in providing and managing the Fox Services.** Fox may make your information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the Fox Services.  

**To allow social sharing functionality.** If you have a social media account and are eligible to log in with or connect a social media service account with a Fox Service, we may share your user name, picture, and likes, as well as your activities and comments with other Fox Services’ users and with your friends associated with your social media service. We may also share the same information with the social media service provider. By logging in with or connecting your Fox Services account with a social media service, you are providing your consent to us to share information we collect from and about you with the social media service provider, other users and your friends and you understand that the social media service’s use of the shared information will be governed by the social media service’s privacy policy.  If you do not want your personal information shared in this way, please do not connect your social media service account with your Fox Services account and do not participate in social sharing on Fox Services. 

**To provide co-branded services and features.** We may offer co-branded services or features, such as contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions together with a third party (“Co-Branded Services”).  These Co-Branded Services may be hosted on Fox Services or on the third party’s service.  By virtue of these relationships, if you are eligible to participate, we may share the information you submit in connection with the Co-Branded Service with the third party (where appropriate).  The third party’s use of your information will be governed by the third party’s privacy policy. 

**To contact you.** Fox may periodically send promotional materials and notifications related to the Fox Services to eligible users. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials, follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of, such as notifications of changes to the Fox Services or policies. If you have installed a mobile app and you wish to stop receiving push notifications, you can change the settings either on your mobile device or through the app. 

**To share with Company Affiliates.** Fox may share eligible users’ information with Company Affiliates for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.  A link to a website that lists Fox Affiliates can be found at the beginning of this policy.  Users who visit Company Affiliates’ services should still refer to their separate privacy policies, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy. 

**To share with business partners.** If you are an eligible user, Fox may share your information with business partners to permit them to send you marketing communications where appropriate. 

**To protect the rights of Fox and others.** There may be instances when Fox may use or disclose your information, including situations where Fox has a good faith belief that such use or disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of Fox, our Company Affiliates or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements and our terms of use); (ii) protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of the Fox Services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; (iv) comply with the law or legal process; or (v) respond to requests from public and government authorities. 

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If Fox sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business (including in connection with a bankruptcy or similar proceedings), Fox may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction. 

## 4\. SECURITY

Fox uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. However, no one can guarantee the complete safety of your information.  

## 5\. USER ACCESS AND CONTROL

If you would like to access, review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise limit our use of your personal information you have previously provided directly to us, you may contact us as outlined in Section 7. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. 

Eligible users who have provided personal information may request that we not share such information on a going-forward basis with Company Affiliates or unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes by sending an email to [californiaprivacy@foxcustomercare.com](mailto:californiaprivacy@foxcustomercare.com), with “Fox Disclosure Opt-out” in the subject line. Please include your full name, email address, postal address and the relevant Fox Service in the body of the email. We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable. 

**Deletion Rights of Minors.** If you are under age 18 and a registered user of the Fox Services, you may ask us to remove content or information that you have posted to the Company Services by writing to [privacypolicy@foxhome.com.](mailto:privacypolicy@foxhome.com) Please note that your request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information, as, for example, some of your content may have been reposted by another user. 

## 6\. OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION

**Updates to Privacy Policy.** Fox may modify this Privacy Policy. Please look at the Effective Date at the top of this Privacy Policy to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Fox Services. 

**Location of Data.** The Fox Services are hosted and managed from the United States. If you are a user located outside the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information processed in the United States. United States data protection and other relevant laws may not be the same as those in your jurisdiction. This includes the use of cookies and other similar technologies as described above. Eligible users, please note that in certain circumstances, courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies or security authorities in the United States may be entitled to access your personal information, if any. As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care. 

**Linked Services.** The Fox Services may also be linked to sites operated by affiliated or unaffiliated companies, and that may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes, or applications developed and maintained by unaffiliated companies. Fox is not responsible for the privacy practices of unaffiliated companies, and once you leave the Fox Services you should check the applicable privacy policy of the other service. 

In addition, Fox is not responsible for the privacy or data security practices of other organizations, such as Facebook, Tumblr, Twitter, Apple, Google, Microsoft or any other app developer, app provider, social media platform provider, operating system provider, wireless service provider, or device manufacturer, including in connection with any information eligible users may disclose to other organizations through or in connection with the Fox Services. 

**Data Retention.** We will retain your information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or allowed by law. 

## 7\. CONTACT US

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

Email: [privacypolicy@foxhome.com](mailto:privacypolicy@foxhome.com)

Mail: Mail/Phone: C/O Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation  
2816 Columbia Street  
Torrance, CA 90503  
(888) 223-4369
